Cook, Alice Papers /3012
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series Series II: Academic Files
  - Sub-Series D. Teaching Files
    - Sub-Series 1. Class Materials
      - Sub-Series a. Lecture Notes
        - Union Functions I (Box 8, Folder 28)
        - Union Government Internal Government Structure (Box 8, Folder 29-30)
        - Union Structure I The Federation: Central and State (Box 9, Folder 1)
        - Union Structure II The National Union (Box 9, Folder 2)
        - Union Typology II Transportation (Box 9, Folder 3)
        - Union Typology III White Collar and Government (Box 9, Folder 4)
        - Union Typology IV (Box 9, Folder 5)
        - Union Typology V (Box 9, Folder 6)
        - Union Typology Building Trades, Maritime Trades, Service Trades (Box 9, Folder 7)
        - Working Mothers ILR 635 (Box 9, Folder 8)
          Women At Work for card file of lecture notes see end of collection Box 125
      - Sub-Series b. Course Materials
        - ILR 200 Labor and Politics, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 9-10)
        - ILR 301 Structure, Government, Administration and Functions of American Trade Unions, 1963-1968 (Box 9, Folder 11-30)
        - ILR 350 Labor Union History, 1955-1960 (Box 10, Folder 1-8)
        - ILR 351 Labor Union Structure, 1956-1961 (Box 10, Folder 9-25)
        - ILR 403 Problems of Union Democracy, 1964-1967 (Box 10, Folder 26-34)
        - ILR 467 Women At Work, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 35)
        - ILR 499 Special Studies, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 36)
        - ILR 505 Labor Union History and Administration, 1966-1968 (Box 10, Folder 37-44)
        - ILR 505 (continued) - Labor Union History and Administration, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 1-13)
        - ILR 507 Labor Theory, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 14)
        - ILR 508 - ?, 1964-1965 (Box 11, Folder 15-16)
        - ILR 550 Labor Union History, 1957-1959 (Box 11, Folder 17-20)
        - ILR 552 Theories of the Labor Movement, 1959-1962 (Box 11, Folder 21-33)
        - ILR 554 Labor Union History and Structure, 1958-1960 (Box 11, Folder 34-36)
        - ILR 602, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 1)
        - ILR 605 Labor and Politics, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 2-10)
        - ILR 606 Labor and Government, 1964-1969 (Box 12, Folder 11-22)
        - ILR 607 Labor in Politics, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 23)
        - ILR 609 Professionals and their Organization, 1965-1971 (Box 12, Folder 24-33)
        - ILR 650 Labor and Government, 1956-1961 (Box 12, Folder 34-41)
          Note: taught with Frances Perkins in 1957
        - ILR 654 Classic Readings in Labor History and Structure, 1956-1958 (Box 13, Folder 1-12)
        - ILR 66X Women at Work (proposed course), 1971 (Box 13, Folder 13)
        - ILR 699 Independent, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 14)
        - Miscellaneous unlabeled (Box 13, Folder 15)
          no date
        - Miscellaneous regarding MILR exams, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 16)
        - Miscellaneous descriptions and schedules, 1955-1962 (Box 13, Folder 17)
        - Miscellaneous Course Outlines Illinois, 1955-1959 (Box 13, Folder 18)
        - Miscellaneous Course NILE, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 19)
          Summer 1961
      - Sub-Series c. Miscellaneous
        - Miscellaneous Course Materials (Box 13, Folder 20-39)
          Courses taught by other ILR faculty (ILR 117, 141, 290, 293, 320, 350, 351, 370, 390, 402, 403, 452, 492, 520, 530, 550, 552, 554, 580)
        - Miscellaneous class handouts (Box 13, Folder 40-48)
    - Sub-Series 2. Student Files
      - Aboud, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 49)
      - Akamatsu, 1964-1965 (Box 13, Folder 50)
      - Aron, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 51)
      - Bachner, 1970-1972 (Box 13, Folder 52)
      - Beaudoin, 1955-1956 (Box 13, Folder 53)
      - Bella, 1957-1961 (Box 13, Folder 54)
      - Bhuchongkul, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 55)
      - Bovajian, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 56)
      - Bridger, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 57)
      - Brockman, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 58)
      - Broty, 1968-1972 (Box 13, Folder 59-60)
      - Castle, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 61)
      - Czamecki, 1956-1970 (Box 13, Folder 62)
      - Dayal, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 63)
      - Doering, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 64)
      - Domingo, 1964-1965 (Box 13, Folder 65)
      - Dotson, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 66)
      - Dyer, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 67)
      - Edgecomb, 1963-1964 (Box 13, Folder 68)
      - Fenily, 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 69)
      - Gately, 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 70)
      - Hayes, 1971-1972 (Box 13, Folder 71)
      - Ferguson, 1954-1962 (Box 13, Folder 72-73)
      - Foster, 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 74)
      - Galvin, 1959-1962 (Box 14, Folder 1-4)
      - Garton, 1958-1959 (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - Gebauer, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - Gettings, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - Goldblatt, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - Goto, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - Hammond, 1957-1963 (Box 14, Folder 10)
      - Harris, 1967-1971 (Box 14, Folder 11)
      - Herman, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 12)
      - Himes, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 13)
      - Kateyama, 1967-1972 (Box 14, Folder 14)
      - Kawai, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 15)
      - Kendellen, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 16)
      - Kim, 1970-1972 (Box 14, Folder 17-19)
      - Kinju, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 20)
      - Kitauva, 1964-1965 (Box 14, Folder 21)
      - Klein, 1958-1959 (Box 14, Folder 22)
      - Kuahava, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 23)
      - Lafferty, 1966-1968 (Box 14, Folder 24)
      - Lee, 1970-1972 (Box 14, Folder 25)
      - Lehrer, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 26)
      - Mannix, 1970-1972 (Box 14, Folder 27)
      - Miller, 1958-1960 (Box 14, Folder 28)
      - Mubarak, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 29)
      - Nevins, 1970-1972 (Box 14, Folder 30)
      - Nolte, 1968-1971 (Box 14, Folder 31)
      - Oh, 1958-1961 (Box 14, Folder 32)
      - Olmedillo, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 32a)
      - Pegnetter, 1968-1969 (Box 14, Folder 34)
      - Penski, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 35-36)
      - Resnick, 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 37)
      - Rothstein, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 38)
      - Rubin, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 39)
      - Said, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 40)
      - Savage, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 41)
      - Scherer, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 42)
      - Shimada, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 43)
      - Stone, 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 44)
      - Strable, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 45)
      - Tambunan, 1959-1960 (Box 14, Folder 46)
      - Tetjasukmana, 1957-1965 (Box 14, Folder 47-48)
      - Torode, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 49)
      - Verma, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 50)
      - DeVincenti, 1959-1972 (Box 14, Folder 51)
      - Wars, 1967-1968 (Box 14, Folder 52-53)
      - Walker, 1964-1967 (Box 14, Folder 54)
      - Weissenberg, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 55)
      - Wolkinson, 1968-1970 (Box 14, Folder 56)
      - Woo, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 57)
      - Woods, 1964-1965 (Box 14, Folder 58)
      - Woolf, 1957-1972 (Box 14, Folder 59)
      - Yamamoto, 1960-1961 (Box 14, Folder 60)
      - Graduate Assistants, 1957-1968 (Box 14, Folder 61)
      - Graduate students, 1964-1967 (Box 14, Folder 62)
      - Undergraduate advisees, 1963-1972 (Box 14, Folder 63)
    - Sub-Series 3. Term Papers and Draft Theses
      - Aboud, Antone (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Brown, Richard (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - Coan, Howard (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Davis, Rina (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - Disini, Domingo (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - Dropkin, David (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - Ferguson, John (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - Finder, Robert (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - Galvin, Miles (Box 15, Folder 9-12)
      - Harvey, Dennis (Box 15, Folder 13-15)
      - Huret, Robert (Box 15, Folder 16)
      - Kaplan, Bennett (Box 15, Folder 17)
      - Karlebach, Roger (Box 15, Folder 18)
      - Kim, Kyung (Box 15, Folder 19)
      - Levin, Edward (Box 15, Folder 20)
      - Liden, Beverly (Box 15, Folder 21)
      - Mandato, Michael (Box 15, Folder 22)
      - Manzer, Jefferson (Box 15, Folder 23)
      - Metchick, Robert (Box 15, Folder 24)
      - Middaugh, Alice (Box 15, Folder 25)
      - Miller, Thomas (Box 15, Folder 26)
      - Miller, Richard (Box 15, Folder 27)
      - Mubarak, Khogali (Box 15, Folder 28)
      - Murray, Vic (Box 15, Folder 29)
      - Muth, John (Box 15, Folder 30)
      - Nathan, Jeanne (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Newton, Guy A. (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - O'Connor, John (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - Ohlweiter, John (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Oshinsky, David (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - Parris, Frederick (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - Penny, Robert (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - Raynolds, Harold (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - Rosenthal, Harriet (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - Rutkin, David (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - Sackman, Samuel (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - Savelson, Robert (Box 16, Folder 12)
      - Schimel, Ruth (Box 16, Folder 13)
      - Small, Jeffrey (Box 16, Folder 14)
      - Smith, Ronald (Box 16, Folder 15)
      - Stross, Peter (Box 16, Folder 16)
      - Szarejko, John (Box 16, Folder 17)
      - Tedyasukmana, Iskandar (Box 16, Folder 18)
      - DeVincenti, Julia (Box 16, Folder 19-29)
      - Walker, Roger (Box 16, Folder 30)
      - Weiner, Carol (Box 16, Folder 31)
      - Yoel, Janice (Box 16, Folder 32)
- Series Series III: Conferences and Programs
  - Faculty-Alumni Seminar, 1960-1964 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    Annual seminar of ILR School held in NYC
  - Female Studies Program, 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    Includes a 7-page critique of the program (by Alice Cook and others)
  - Home Economics Seminar, 1956-1967 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Human Resources Workshop, 1996-1997 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    Cornell: The Big Picture Alice Cook, served as a panel member
  - Japan Institute of Labor, 1965-1966 (Box 17, Folder 5-7)
    Joint research program between ILR, CU and Japan Institute of Labor
  - Manpower Studies Conference, 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    Conference held during 25th Anniversary of ILR School celebration. Includes School plans and proposals for the 25th Anniversary.
  - National Institute for Labor Education (NILE), 1961-1963 (Box 17, Folder 9-16)
    Residential Study Institutes held at ILR School, includes reports, memos, class projects and other related materials
  - Union University Urban Affairs Programs, 1964-1969 (Box 17, Folder 17-20)
    Joint endeavor of many metropolitan NY labor unions and The Metropolitan District Office of ILR. Includes information on courses, reports, memos, proposals, programs, lecture notes, and other related materials
  - Womanpower Conferences, 1969-1971 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    Includes draft proposal, summary of workshop, memos and other related materials
- Series Series IV: Professional Files
  - AFL-CIO Labor Studies Center Program, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - AAUP Committee on Women, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Advisory Committee on Student Labor Dialogue (International Union of Electrical Workers), 1971 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - American Federation of Teachers, Local 189 Friedmann Committee, 1965-1967 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - American Society for Public Administration Conference, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Binghamton Conference, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Centavo Foundation, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Cogen, Charles Committee, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Educational Testing Service, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - First International Centennial, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Fund for International Social and Economic Education, 1966-1968 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Harvard University Institute for Educational Management, 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 13-15)
  - Industrial Relations Research Association, 1959-1971 (Box 18, Folder 16-17)
  - International Industrial Relations Association, 1967-1971 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - International Society of Food Service Consultants Seminar, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - International Symposium on Public Employment and Labor Relations, 1969-1971 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Ithaca Neighborhood Center, 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Keast Commission on Academic Tenure, 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Labor Leader Series, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - National Institute of Labor Education, 1959-1964 (Box 18, Folder 24-26)
  - N.Y.S. Joint Legislative Committee on the Taylor Law, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - N.Y.S. University Faculty Senate, 1967-1970 (Box 18, Folder 28-31)
  - Presidents Commission on the Status of Women. Education Committee Eleanor Roosevelt, Chairman of Commission), 1962 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Sloan Foundation Research Network on Work Redesign and Work Family, 1995-1996 (Box 18, Folder 33-37)
  - Status of Working Women in Japan, U.S. and Canada, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 37A-B)
    Program held in Honolulu AC was a participant
  - SUNY Asian Studies Faculty Committee, 1967-1971 (Box 18, Folder 38-40)
  - Tompkins County CLU Executive Board, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - UAW Public Review Board, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 42-44)
  - Women in Law and Life, 1967-1968 (Box 18, Folder 45)
- Series Series V: Arbitration and Mediation Files
  - American Airlines, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - American Arbitration Association, 1971-1972 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - American Federation of Teachers Public Review Board, 1965-1969 (Box 19, Folder 3-4)
    Includes proposal for a public review board, reports and correspondence. (3page letter. dated 5/16/68 from Alice Cook to UFT Board member regarding the problem of discipline) and other related
  - Erie County Community College vs. County of Erie, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 5-8)
    3/2/71 Fact-finding hearing. Includes report, correspondence, and related documents
  - Griffith Institute and Central School District vs. Griffith Faculty Association, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    6/1/1971 Includes report and related documents.
  - New York State Public Employment Relations Board, 1968-1972 (Box 19, Folder 10-12)
    Includes correspondence, memos, notes, certificates, and other related administrative material
  - Ontario Public School, Margaret Tomen, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    Includes an affidavit (Supreme Court of Ontario) by Alice Cook regarding the rejection of Tomen's membership on the grounds she was female
  - Stanford University Grievance Arbitration Panel, 1971-1972 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    Includes correspondence, policies, procedures, information
  - Waterloo Board of Education vs. Waterloo Education Association, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 15-16)
    6/5/1970 Includes F-F report and related materials
- Series Series VI: Subject Files
  - Sub-Series A. U.S. Files
    - Abortion (Box 20, Folder 1-2)
    - Academic - CU (Cornell University) and Others (Box 20, Folder 3-6)
    - Age discrimination (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Affirmative action (Box 20, Folder 8-15)
    - Affirmative Action Cases (Box 20, Folder 16-20)
    - Affirmative Action Remedies (Box 20, Folder 21-22)
    - Affirmative Action-Reverse Discrimination (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - American Association of University Women (AAUW) (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Asian Americans (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Bias (Box 20, Folder 26-27)
    - Bibliography (Box 20, Folder 28-34)
    - Block studies - CU (Box 20, Folder 35-36)
    - Black Workers - Listing (Box 21, Folder 1-2)
    - Blacks (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Blue collar (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Budget (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Business (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Child Care (Box 21, Folder 7-23)
    - Child Welfare (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Civil Rights Update (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Class (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Coalition of Labor Union Women (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - College Bargaining (Box 21, Folder 28-30)
    - Community Action (Box 21, Folder 31-32)
    - Community Service (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Computers (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Corporations (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Culture (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Demography (Box 21, Folder 37-41)
    - Demography (Box 22, Folder 1-3)
    - Demographic Data, 1986-1990 (Box 22, Folder 4-5)
    - Demographic Data, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 6-7)
    - Discrimination (Box 22, Folder 8-20)
    - Discrimination-Academia (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Discrimination-Ageism (Box 22, Folder 22-23)
    - Discrimination-Education of Women (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Discrimination-litigation (Box 22, Folder 25-26)
    - Discrimination-NLRB (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Discrimination, 1981-1990 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Discrimination-Remedies (Box 23, Folder 1-3)
    - Diversity (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - U.S. Economic Policy (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - U.S. Economics (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Education (Box 23, Folder 7-16)
    - Education and Training of Women (Box 23, Folder 17-19)
    - Education-Discrimination (Box 23, Folder 20-22)
    - Higher Education (Box 23, Folder 23-25)
    - Education-Preschool-8th Grade (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Education-Vocational (Box 23, Folder 27-28)
    - Education-Vocational Training (Box 23, Folder 29-30)
    - Education-Women, Vocational (Box 23, Folder 31-33)
    - Education of Women- Vocational Education and Training (Box 24, Folder 1-3)
    - Education-Women's studies (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - EEO (Equal Employment Opportunity) (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - EEO-Remedies (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - EEOC (Equal Employment Opportunity Commission) (Box 24, Folder 7-16)
    - EEOC and Unions (Box 24, Folder 17-18)
    - EEOC-Compliances (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - EEOC Regulations (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - EEOC Remedies (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - EEOC-Title VII (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Equal Opportunity (Box 24, Folder 23-24)
    - Equal Rights Amendment (ERA) (Box 24, Folder 25-30)
    - ERA and Right Wing, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Equality (Box 25, Folder 1-5)
    - Equality and athletics (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Equality-Remedies (Box 25, Folder 7-9)
    - Ethical Practices-Corruption (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Family-Unions (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Family (Box 25, Folder 12-14)
    - Family-Abortion (Box 25, Folder 15-16)
    - Family-Adoption (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Family-Advocacy (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Family-Afro-America (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Family-Aging (Box 25, Folder 20-21)
    - Family and Child Care, 1989-1990 (Box 25, Folder 22-23)
    - Family and Child Care, 1991-1995 (Box 25, Folder 24-25)
    - Family and Divorce Law (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Family and Work (Box 25, Folder 27-33)
    - Family-Bibliography (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - Family-Benefits (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - Family-Bias (Box 25, Folder 36)
    - Family-Birth Control (Box 25, Folder 37)
    - Family-Breast feeding (Box 25, Folder 38)
    - Family-Careers (Box 25, Folder 39)
    - Family-Characteristics (Box 25, Folder 40)
    - Family-Child Abuse (Box 25, Folder 41)
    - Family-Child care (Box 25, Folder 42)
    - Family-Child care, 1986-1988 (Box 25, Folder 43-46)
    - Family-Child care, 1981-1985 (Box 25, Folder 47)
    - Family-Child care, 1981-1985 (Box 26, Folder 1-2)
    - Family-Child care, 1975-1980 (Box 26, Folder 3-4)
    - Family-Child labor (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Family-Childless (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Family-Child Support (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Family-Children general (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Family-class (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Family-costs (Box 26, Folder 10-11)
    - Family-Cornell University (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Family-corporations (Box 26, Folder 13-18)
    - Family-Culture (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Family-Demography (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Family-Dependents-Elderly (Box 26, Folder 21-23)
    - Family-Dependent Care (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Family-Disabled (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Family-Displaced Homemaker (Box 26, Folder 26-27)
    - Family-Divorce Law (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Family-Domestic Partner (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - Family-Double Burden (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - Family-Dual Careers (Box 26, Folder 31-32)
    - Family-Eating (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - Family-Economics (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - Family-Education (Box 26, Folder 35)
    - Family-Elder (Box 26, Folder 36)
    - Family-Equal Pay (Box 26, Folder 37)
    - Family-Equality (Box 26, Folder 38)
    - Family-Flexible Schedules (Box 26, Folder 39-41)
    - Family-Food stamps (Box 26, Folder 42)
    - Family-Future (Box 26, Folder 43)
    - Family-General (Box 26, Folder 44-49)
    - Family-Grandparents (Box 26, Folder 50)
    - Family-Health and Safety (Box 27, Folder 1-2)
    - Family-Home based work (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Family-Homeless (Box 27, Folder 4-5)
    - Family-Homosexual (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Family-Hours and schedules, adoptions (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Family-Hours of work (Box 27, Folder 8-9)
    - U.S. Family-Household (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Family-Housing (Box 27, Folder 11-12)
    - Family-Immigration (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Family-Income (Box 27, Folder 14-15)
    - Family-Intermarriage (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Family-LMPr (Labor Market Practice) (Box 27, Folder 17-18)
    - Family-LMPr Non-traditional (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Family-LMPr poverty, minorities (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Family-LMPr single head household (Box 27, Folder 21-22)
    - Family-Latinos (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Family-Law (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Family-Law, pregnancy, property (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Family-Leaves (Box 27, Folder 26-34)
    - Family-Leisure (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - Family-Married women, mothers (Box 27, Folder 36)
    - Family, Marriage (Box 27, Folder 37)
    - Family-Maternity leave (Box 27, Folder 38-40)
    - Family-Men (Box 27, Folder 41-42)
    - Family-Minorities (Box 27, Folder 43)
    - Family-Midwives (Box 27, Folder 44)
    - Family-Mobility (Box 27, Folder 45)
    - Family-Mommy track (Box 27, Folder 46)
    - Family-Motherhood (Box 27, Folder 47)
    - Family-Nutrition (Box 27, Folder 48)
    - Family-Other countries (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Family-Parenthood (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Family-Pensions (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Family-Planning (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Family-Policy (Box 28, Folder 5-7)
    - Family-Politics (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Family-Poverty, 1988-1997 (Box 28, Folder 9-16)
    - Family-Pregnancy (Box 28, Folder 17-18)
    - Family-Protective legislation (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Family-Rights (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Family-Remedies (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Family-Research (Box 28, Folder 22-23)
    - Family-Rural women (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Family-Sandwich generation (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Family-Self employment (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Family-Social Security (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - Family-Substance abuse (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - Family-Taxes (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - Family-Teens (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - Family-Theory (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - Family-Trade Unions (Box 28, Folder 32-35)
    - Family-Trade unions- Coalition of Labor Union Women (CLUW) (Box 28, Folder 36)
    - Family-Transportation (Box 28, Folder 37)
    - Family-Twins (Box 28, Folder 38)
    - Family-Values (Box 28, Folder 39)
    - Family-Violence (Box 28, Folder 40)
    - Family-Volunteers (Box 28, Folder 41)
    - Family-Wages (Box 28, Folder 42)
    - Family-Welfare (Box 28, Folder 43)
    - Family-Work (Box 28, Folder 44)
    - Family-Workforce (Box 28, Folder 45)
    - Foundations-Sloan (Box 28, Folder 46)
    - Foundations (Box 28, Folder 47)
    - Future (women's rights) (Box 28, Folder 48)
    - General-U.S. (Box 29, Folder 1-11)
    - Harassment (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Hawaii-Affirmative Action (Box 29, Folder 13-14)
    - Hawaii-Affirmative action and public employment (Box 29, Folder 15-19)
    - Hawaii-Affirmative action procedures (Box 29, Folder 20-22)
    - Hawaii-Comparable Worth (Box 30, Folder 1-4)
    - Hawaii-Demographics (Box 30, Folder 5-7)
    - Hawaii-Education of women (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Hawaii-Equal opportunity (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Hawaii-Family corporation (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Hawaii-General (Box 30, Folder 11-15)
    - Hawaii-LMPr (Labor Market Practice) (Box 30, Folder 16-17)
    - Hawaii-Laws (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Hawaii-Health and Safety (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Hawaii-Legislature (Box 30, Folder 20-21)
    - Hawaii, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 22-23)